Seriously...
You sure you've got Wrath and not Gluttony?
He gave us all those supplies...
Just how much do you need to eat?
Rage burns a lot of calories.
You guys did this already.
Here.
You can have some, so don't get mad.
Say, "Ahh."
Ahh...
Now chew.
Good boy.
What's with that?
Uh... Why are you sleeping on my lap?
Floor's too hard to sleep on.
This bed's decent.
Well, excuse me for only being decent!
Worst part is it won't shut up...
Listen, you...
And she's already asleep.
Looking at her now, she seems like a kid.
I'm a phantom who's not allowed to die.
There's something I need to do.
Say, Greed... what exactly
is she fighting against?
Are you clamming up
when you actually know again?
Maybe. But if you keep
traveling together, you'll get an idea.
Just don't dig too deep.
Well, that reeks of trouble...
When are we going to reach Galia, Lady Roxy?
We should be nearing the border already.
Isn't that right, Mugan?
Right. We're almost at Hausen.
The Village of Lost Memories
Wow! Look at that castle, Lady Roxy!
This is the seat of
the Barbatos lands, Hausen.
I recall Sir Aaron previously lived there.
Previously?
Who's the lord of the castle now?
I believe a lich lord crowned
beast has taken it over.
A c-crowned beast?!
Yeah. Apparently.
Looking up close, it's all busted up...
But I don't sense a monster.
Seems like it must've
been liberated recently.
Welcome to Hausen.
I am Aaron Barbatos.
You didn't retire?!
Miria...
It's an honor, sir.
I never thought I'd ever meet Aaron Barbatos,
head of the Barbatos family,
one of the five great estates,
and the expert swordsman
called the Blade of Light.
I apologize for the sudden intrusion. I'm—
You certainly have grown, Roxy Hart.
You know of me?
I'm an old acquaintance of Mason and Aisha.
They actually asked me to name you
when you were born.
I never knew! My parents
hadn't mentioned that before.
I'm jealous, Lady Roxy!
You were named by a hero.
Truly!
Former hero, really.
Surely you've heard
the reason I retired, Roxy.
Yes...
With the loss of those
I should have protected,
I no longer have a reason to fight.
But... you did dispose of the lich lord, yes?
Not alone.
It's thanks to the man who fought at my side.
Even if you were fighting together,
he must be quite the talented warrior
to slay a crowned beast.
Where is this guy? I wanna meet him!
He's taken his leave.
Could you tell me his name?
I'll need to report to the capital how
the lich lord has been driven from Hausen.
Sadly, I can't do that, Roxy.
If someone comes here asking about me,
would you tell them you don't know?
Sorry to ask you such a weird request...
He requested I keep his name
a secret. My apologies.
I see...
I understand. And I beg your
pardon for the intrusion.
If you'll excuse us.
You're heading to Galia?
How did you know that? I never mentioned it.
I can only imagine one reason a young
holy knight like yourself would be out here.
Did the Vlericks send you?
No, sir. I volunteered.
You were manipulated into doing so.
The Harts and the Barbatoses
have always been annoyances.
Regardless, I will protect the people.
I have simply inherited my father's ideals.
Mason's gone?
Would you be willing
to accept my instruction?
I'll teach you how to fight in Galia.
I did give you that name, after all.
I couldn't ask for more! Yes, gladly!
This isn't what I signed up for!
Quit whining and keep working, Miria!
I can see Mason's teachings
in your swordplay.
Very good. You've got a good touch.
And I like the look in your eyes.
I need to become much stronger!
To protect everyone!
We've been walking since the last stop...
What is this place, Myne?
It looks abandoned...
or maybe more like ruined.
This is where I was born.
I was taken to the imperial capital right
after I was born, so I don't remember it.
But it's important.
The imperial capital...?
I thought Galia collapsed 4,000 years ago!
Hey!
There.
A cocoon...?
Great. I can't believe one survived...
Greed, what is that thing?
A chimera.
It was a biological weapon
Galia's military tested out in the old days.
They take a vessel and
essentially sew monsters into it.
A chimera...
It's a damn failure is what it is.
And they were supposed to
have all been shut down...
It's time you paid me back.
So, we're fighting this thing?
Chimera Haniel
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Chimera... Haniel.
It's giving me an error for its skills!
All those monsters mixed together
mean it's too unstable to read.
Those are some incredible stats, too.
This one's still in a larval state,
so we can beat it.
It's not fully grown?!
What do I need to do?
As long as its soul is intact, you can
damage its body, but it won't die.
Its soul...
So you want me to use the soul-eating
part of Gluttony's power?
Right. The most sinful and heretical
of all the Skills of Deadly Sin.
Okay, battle starts now.
What a jump!
Th-This is a chimera...?
Why's there a person in its chest?!
The same red eyes I have?
It was just intimidating you.
Come on, don't look right at her,
or you'll be too frozen up to move.
That's just sad...
Myne, just who is she?
The core of the chimera.
I need you to finish her off.
But... if I eat her soul...
She'll be suffering in eternal
torment forever, right?
I can't do that...
Don't let appearances fool you.
That's nothing more than a monster
wearing human skin at this point.
There's no other way to stop it.
If you keep being naive, you'll die.
Greed! I need the black scythe!
This magic attack works indirectly
by doing damage with the lava!
The black scythe won't be able to cut it off!
Myne?!
Stay back, Fate.
Damn...
Let's split up.
Got it!
Take this!
Good! The petrifying magic arrows worked.
That should slow her down.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, it's a little
too soon to celebrate.
She can regenerate.
A weapon capable of non-stop fighting
with no support... That's what a chimera is.
How are we supposed to beat it, then?
Is Myne hitting harder than before?
Yeah. Sloth becomes heavier
and more powerful with every swing.
The downside being how it cuts down
on your agility in the process.
What's this bizarre pressure?!
It's undergoing metamorphosis.
Get behind me.
Am I being protected again?
Can I really hold my head high and claim
to be helping Lady Roxy like this?
I want to change...
I want to be someone with power, too!
Myne. I'm going to go
into a half-starvation state.
If you're not careful and tap too deeply,
Gluttony will overwhelm you.
Yeah. I know.
But at this rate, I'll be useless!
If I screw this up, it's over...
Have to control it!
Myne.
Fate?
You don't have to act so surprised.
Did you really think I couldn't do it?
Now... let's start fighting back!
Feathers?
They explode on contact.
Perfect. I'll make good use of them, then.
Clever! I think I get what you're after!
Then let's get right to it.
And it's in the perfect position!
Let's throw Sandstorm on there too.
Take 10% of my stats!
Deal!
Bloody Ptarmigan!
Now!
Sloth, awaken.
Damn, that's powerful!
Hey, stupid! This is no time to be impressed!
Let's end this before it can regenerate!
Right!
Huh, a barrier created with a skill.
Sounds like a job
for the black scythe, then.
Even the black scythe can't get through?
You need to read the flow of magic power
and aim for the weakest point!
The flow of magic power?
That must be it! The weak point...
is right here!
Stop! Don't look at me!
Fate, stop!
She's getting away!
Looks like you're reaching your limit...
No time. Get on.
On the axe...?
I'll send you into the sky with this.
Hurry.
Before Haniel recovers.
Got it...
Just wondering, how do we
beat her once we catch up?
Great news! You can now use my
second level's secret technique.
How's 20% of your stats sound?
Fine, take it!
Aim for where the center
of the magic power is!
Look carefully, now!
The center...
Where the magic power is flowing from.
There!
She caught me in the barrier?!
This is bad! Haniel's going to cook
herself and take you with her!
Then we feast before we burn!
Listen to you!
Let's do this!
Deadly Inferno!
What is this...?
Did my Telepathy skill activate?
Who's that?
Gluttony skill has activated.
I'm not feeling the usual exhilaration...
If anything, there's this...
chest-tightening sadness.
That sounds right.
Deteriorated or not, you did
just eat one of your own kind.
There's no pleasure to be had there.
One of my own...?
Did you know her?
I've forgotten what happened
all those years ago.
But...
If someone becomes a chimera,
you have to kill them.
Otherwise, even more people die.
That could be me one day...
Hey, Myne. I'd like to ask a favor.
What is it?
If I ever lose control of myself...
Please, kill me.
You're the only one who can
stop me if I go berserk.
So... please.
Myne?
Okay. If it happens, I'll kill you.
Sorry.
And thank you.
I'm heading on to Babylon. What about you?
Still have work to do.
I promised the others I'd build
a village just for us.
You actually meant that?
Before we meet again...
I get the feeling...
You'll be dead, Fate.
Ta-da! Say hello to level 3,
the magic shield.
Unlocking a new level in a place
like this, resetting all your stats...
It's ridiculous.
Hey, wait, Myne!
Could you help me hunt so
I can get my stats back up?
For how many gold coins?
Ugh, you... you're so stingy!
Sure am.
This is Babylon.
The bulwark between the kingdom and
Galia... the Sentinel City, Babylon.
The walls, made out of adamantine alloy,
have lasted for millennia
against the attacks of Galia's monsters.
Wait, why are you going that way?
Other way around!
There's gotta be a gate
on the south side, too.
There's only a northern gate for Babylon.
Galia's to the south, after all.
Why would you build a gate there?
It'd practically be an opening
for monsters to get in through.
You seem well-informed.
Have you been here before?
Well, a little bit,
with my previous wielder.
If they wielded you, Greed,
did they have a Skill of Deadly Sin too?
Yep, but they up and died,
left me behind.
I see...
Humans are mortal.
That means dying one day.
That's just how it works.
Not that being immortal
is all roses, mind you.
You're always having to say goodbye.
I guess so.
Wait, you can't die?
Didn't I mention it?
The Weapons of Mortal Sin
can't be destroyed.
Really?
Hey, look there. That's
the northern gate of Babylon.
The meat skewers cost five times
as much as in the capital?!
Cost comes from extra work.
It's quite a trek to get supplies
all the way down here.
Make way!
Babylon's new lord has come
from the royal capital!
That emblem... Where is she?
You're too worked up. Settle down some.
How could I?!
It's Lady Roxy!
Lady Roxy!
Well, go on, Fate, wave.
Don't be ridiculous.
Going to die...
Did I just imagine that?
Roxy...
is going to die here.
The Guardian of Lust
"The Guardian of Lust."